

### **CONTACT**

- **+91-8866266408**
- ☑ 3443mohit@gmail.com
- Uncha Timba, Chaani, Vadodara
- mohit-design.github.io/mohit7design

#### **EDUCATION**

2012 - 2016

Dr. Jivraj Mehta Institute of Technology

- Bachelor in Computer Science and Engineering
- CGPA: 7.25 / 10

2012

**New English Day School** 

- H.S.C.
- Result: 74.67%

2010

**Bharat High School** 

- H.S.C.
- Result: 79.38%

#### **SOFT SKILLS**

- Adaptability
- Problem Solving
- Creative Thinking
- Teamwork
- Leadership
- Time Management
- Listening

# **MOHIT PATEL**

## WEB DESIGNER CUM UI/UX DESIGNER

### **PROFILE**

I am a highly competent IT professional with a proven track record in Web Designing and UI/UX Designing. I have 7+ years of experience in the design field. I have strong technical skills as well as excellent interpersonal skills, enabling me to interact with a wide range of clients. I am eager to be challenged in order to grow and further improve my IT skills. My greatest passion is in life is using my technical know-how to benefit other people and organization.

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

•	• <b>Qualifacts</b> Web Designer	FEB 2021 - PRESENT
	Hi-Lab Solution UI/UX Designer	JULY 2019 - FEB 2021
	Wan Buffer UI/UX Designer	AUG 2018 - APR 2019
	Innowyn Business Solutions Frontend Developer	MAY 2017 - JULY 2018
•	Maxgen Technology Pvt Ltd Web Designer	JULY 2016 - MAY 2017

#### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

- HTML/HTML-5
- CSS/CSS-3
- LESS
- SASS/SCSS
- Bootstrap-3/4/5
- Javascript
- ¡Query
- PSD to HTML
- XD to HTML
- Figma to HTML
- Zeplin to HTML
- InVision to HTML
- Website Design

- Responsive Design
- SVG / GSAP Animation
- Social Media Post Design
- Design Systems and Guidelines
- Wireframe Design
- Mobile Application Design
- Prototyping
- Accessibility Design
- Visual Design
- Design Thinking
- User Centered Design
- Agile/Scrum Methodologies
- React JS (Beginner)

## **TOOLS**

- Adobe Photoshop
- Adobe Illustrator
- Adobe XD
- Figma

- Visual Studio Code
- Sublime Text Editor
- GitHub
- Azure DevOps

#### **SOCIAL PLATFORMS**

- www.linkedin.com/in/mohit-patel-0ba505123/
- <u>www.github.com/mohit-design</u>
- www.behance.net/mohit7design

# PROFESSIONAL ACHIEVEMENTS

- I have been rewarded as a **Best Team Player** in January 2023 from Qualifacts.
- I have been rewarded as a Ace of Initiative in July 2023 from Qualifacts.
- I won the Hackathon event held at Qualifacts.
- I have received an Badge from GitHub community.
- I have passed the CSS skill test and rank in the top 1% of designers worldwide on UXCEL.

#### **PORTFOLIO LINKS**

- mohit-design.github.io/form/signin
- mohit-design.github.io/scroll-based-image-animation
- mohit-design.github.io/scrolling-text-animation
- mohit-design.github.io/button-hover-effect-using-js
- mohit-design.github.io/button-sound-effect
- mohit-design.github.io/place-video-inside-text
- mohit-design.github.io/svg-stroke-animation-one
- mohit-design.github.io/svg-stroke-animation-two
- mohit-design.github.io/water-ripple-effect